playeuromillions.com 2019-04-14

# Privacy Policy

The Company Respects Your Privacy

Secure View Services Ltd, a company registered in Cyprus with company number HE149654 whose registered office is at 3rd Floor, Methonis Tower, 73 Archbishop Makarios Avenue, 2082, Nicosia, Cyprus, along with its subsidiaries, divisions, affiliates and any associated companies, i.e. any company within  the group of companies and/or any company necessary to give effect to the transaction between the parties (" **the Company** "), understands the importance of protecting and safeguarding your privacy when you use our website. 

This Privacy Policy informs you of our privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way information about you, including from your online activity is collected and how that information is used by the Company.

When you use our website (or interact with us through any other means in respect of our website) you shall be asked to provide us with personal identifiable information (" **Personal Information** "). 

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information" means information about a natural person that is readily identifiable to that specific individual.  Personal Information includes, among other information, an individual’s name, address, social security number, telephone number, date of birth, password information, and any other personally identifiable information.  A domain name or Internet protocol address is not considered Personal Information.

This privacy policy tells you about the information the Company may collect on this website, how the information is used, how you can access and correct certain information that we may collect and how we safeguard your Personal Information for the purpose of offering you our services. 

If you as a visitor choose to register or submit information to the Company via this website (the “Site”), you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this privacy policy. Please note that this Site contains links to other websites, including, without limitation, websites maintained by the Company, and other affiliated entities of the Company. Also note that the Company may use third parties to host all or portions of, or to assist in maintaining, the Company websites. 

This Privacy Policy describes the Company’s privacy practices regarding information collected at any time through any means.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “you” or “your” means each person, group of individuals, entity or entities

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please direct your questions to us using the appropriate email link set forth in the "[Contact Us](https://www.playhugelottos.com/en/contact.html "Contact Us")" section.

You acknowledge that you have read and accept the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.

**English and Translated Versions**

If you are reading a translation of this Privacy Policy in a language other than English, you acknowledge and agree that (i) the English version is the official version; (ii) the non-English version is provided for your convenience only and the translation will not be valid as an agreement; and (iii) in the event of any inconsistency between the English and a non-English version, the English version will prevail and govern.

**Personal Identifiable Information Collection**

The Company collects, exports, and uses personal information to manage your relationship with the Company and better serve you by personalizing your experience and interaction with the Company. Such collection is done with appropriate notice and consent, along with required filings with data protection authorities, where required.

The Company may collect your personal information through your access and use of website, web-based applications, or mobile applications, during conversations or correspondence with the Company representatives, or when you purchase goods or services or complete an online application form.

The Company may collect personal information from you in connection with:

• product or service orders, activations, and registrations

• profile creation and user verification for online services

• information requests or complaints

• marketing, newsletter or support subscriptions

• contest entries or survey participation

• visits or browsing on the Company websites

The type of personal information the Company may collect from you includes:

• personal and business contact information, such as name, birthdate, address, telephone number, and email address

• financial information, such as your credit/debit card number or other billing information

• other unique information such as user IDs and passwords, product functionality, product and service preferences, contact preferences, educational and employment background

• geo-location data such as your IP address or physical location when you request location based services

• details of the products and services you have purchased from us or which you have enquired about, together with any additional information necessary to provide those products and services and to respond to your enquiries

• any additional information relating to you that you provide to us directly through our websites or indirectly through use of our websites or online presence, through our representatives or otherwise

• information you provide to us through our service centre or customer surveys from time to time

We do not usually seek sensitive information (for example, data relating to race or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, criminal record, physical or mental health or sexual orientation) from Site visitors. We will, where necessary, obtain your explicit consent to collect and use such information. 

The Company may also collect some information that is not personal information because it does not identify you or anyone else. For example, we may collect anonymous answers to surveys or aggregated information about how users use our websites, products or services.

**Why we collect your Personal Information & The Way We Use Personal Information**

The Company may use a Player’s Personal Information for various purposes including, but not limited to, the following: 

• set up and run a Player’s account to play games online and/or by Direct Debit

• to administer Player Accounts

• provide our services and games

• enable Players to play our games or avail themselves of our services

• notify Players if they win, about changes or information relating to a Player’s account, or changes to our services

• ensure the website is optimised to enable the best experience for you while playing our games

• to contact Players and Persons in response to inquiries, comments and suggestions

• to otherwise contact Players

• for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered

• to track Player use of the Website for internal market research

• to improve the Website and the services we promote or provide through the Website

• to notify Players about promotions, special offers, etc. regarding products and services provided by the Company or its agents

• to be provided to the Third Party Service Providers in connection with the legitimate business purposes of the Company, its Contractors or the Website

• to enforce this Privacy Policy

• as required by law or regulation, or as requested by government or regulatory authorities, including but not limited to gaming regulators

• in connection with an acquisition, merger, restructuring, sale or other transfer involving all or any portion of the business associated with the Website

By submitting foregoing information, a Person will be deemed to have consented to its use for such purposes.

Personal Information collected on this Site may be stored and processed in the United Kingdom or any other country in which the Company (or its affiliates, subsidiaries, and divisions and their respective third party business partners, affiliates and suppliers) maintain facilities. This may include transfer to countries without data protection rules similar to those in effect in your country of residence. You acknowledge and agree that by providing Personal Information to the Company through this Site, you consent to the transmission of such Personal Information over international borders as necessary for processing your requests.

**The Parties To Whom Your Information is Disclosed  **

By voluntarily submitting your Personal Information, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Accordingly, your Personal Information may be disclosed for processing to any of the following persons or entities: (i) any companies within our group and their employees who have a need to know such information; (ii) any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of our companies; (iii) any payment processors who assist us in receiving and making payments to and from you; (iv) people and organisations who provide a service to us or are acting as our agents, on the understanding that they will keep the information confidential; and (v) anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer all or any part of our business or assets, from whom we acquire any business or assets or who acquires substantially all of the assets of the Company. Any processing performed by any of the aforementioned persons or entities will, if required by law, be governed by an agreement protecting your Personal Information.  

Due to the existing legal, regulatory, and security environment, the Company may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose aggregate level and/or personally identifiable information submitted to the Company through the Site. The Company will use reasonable efforts to limit such disclosures to the following circumstances: (i) where the Company believes in good faith that it is required to do so in response to a subpoena or other legal process; (ii) where reasonably required to do so in order to maintain, update or otherwise implement the Company’s data security measures, equipment, technical operations and the like; (iii) where reasonably necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities to preserve and/or enforce the Company’s rights, including but not limited to enforcing the Terms of Use for this Site; (iv) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company; or (v) in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the public or of users of the Company products, services, and the Site. 

In addition, the Company may also disclose Personal Information in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the Company business or any part thereof, or as part of a security audit. 

**Children / Minor's Privacy**

The Company does not knowingly collect information from minors as defined by local law, and does not target its websites or mobile applications to minors under these ages. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online and mobile activities and interests.

**Your Rights in relation to your Personal Information**

You can write to us at any time to obtain a copy of your Personal Information and to have any details thereof amended. 

**Security & Protection of Your Personal Information**

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard all the Personal Information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. 

The Company undertakes substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of the Personal Information, preferences and other information it has collected through this Site and will never knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside the Company other than as described herein. The Company has made a substantial investment in its server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect the information assets of the Company network, including the confidentiality of Personal Information collected through this Site. These technologies are deployed as part of a sophisticated security architecture and protocol.

You should also do your part in protecting your information. Your Company username and any password (if such is provided or enacted) are confidential, and we recommend that you not divulge them to anyone. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet as a public transmission network, neither the Company’s network nor data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect Personal Information that is transmitted to us by you, the Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information. Thus, any Personal Information transmitted to us is done so at your own risk. Once we receive Personal Information, the Company undertakes substantial efforts to protect the confidentiality of this information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Cookies**

We (and/ or other parties whom we duly authorise to do so (for example, third- party advertising services)) use cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services. 

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and you will find cookies at most major websites. Cookies help the Company to tailor information to your preferences and to see which areas of the website are frequented most. The Company never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can change your browser settings to refuse cookies. However, in so doing, you may not be able to fully utilize the Site. For legitimate security reasons, we may refuse access to specific website content unless you accept the use of a cookie or similar device. 

**Banner Ads**

Banner ads will be used to advertise the Company products.  The Company Website will track the number of clicks on such ads for analytical and marketing purposes.

**Data Retention**

The Personal Information that you submit to the Company will only be retained for as long as required for the purposes for which it was collected or as required by law.

**Intellectual Property  **

The entire content of the Site is subject to copyright with all rights reserved and it may only be stored, held or used for your personal use. You may not download (all or in part) for non-personal use or otherwise reproduce, transmit or modify the site without our prior permission. However, you may print out part or all of the Site for your own personal use. These permissions are revocable by us at any time. You are granted a non-exclusive license of those rights in order to view this site on a non-commercial basis only, revocable at any time.

**Security  **

You must ensure that viruses, trojans, worms or equivalent or similar items do not enter your computer system. We assume no responsibility for loss of whatever nature, howsoever arising, resulting from such viruses, trojans, worms or equivalent or similar items.

**Links to Non-THE COMPANY Websites**

The Company sites or services may provide links to third-party applications, products, services, or websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Company site. The Company does not control those third party sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from the Company's practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party sites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by the Company Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any site you interact with before allowing the collection and use of your personal information.

We may also provide social media features that enable you to share information with your social networks and to interact with the Company on various social media sites. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We similarly encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings on the social media sites with which you interact to make sure you understand the information that may be collected, used, and shared by those sites.

**Choices Regarding Use of Personal Information (Opt-Out)**

Upon voluntarily providing your Personal Information to the Company through this Site, the Company will use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Should you at any time decide that you do not want to continue to receive electronic communications, you will have the ability to unsubscribe or “opt out” from such communications by means of a link provided in each such communication, or if not provided therein, by sending an email or contacting us at the contact details provided in the "[Contact Us](https://www.playhugelottos.com/en/contact.html "Contact Us")" section.

**Accuracy, Access and Updated to Your Personal Information**

The Company aims to keep your Personal Information as accurate as possible. Should you at any time desire to review, correct or update your Personal Information, you may update your relevant profile or registration (when applicable) or contact us using the contact information outlined in the "Contact Us" section; the Company will comply with such requests as soon as commercially reasonable or determined by statutory law. In order to ensure the safety of Personal Information, please note you will be subject to providing sufficient evidence of your identity at the time of any such request before any Personal Information records will be made available by the Company.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The Company reserves the right to change, amend or modify this policy at any time and without prior notice to you in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. Please check the Privacy Policy frequently for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. The Company will take reasonable measures to notify you if there is a material change in our privacy practices with respect to use of the information you have provided to the Company. The Company will conspicuously post these changes in our Privacy Policy. The Company also will post a message on the homepage of its Site that states that the Privacy Policy has been changed, and will provide a link to the Privacy Policy.

**Calls**

We may record and monitor calls made or received by us to maintain high quality service standards, to check instructions and for your protection and ours.

**General Principles  **

The Company is committed to safeguarding the privacy of your information. By "your information" we mean any information about you, which you or third parties provide to us. This policy relates to the privacy of your information and outlines our commitment to the secure and responsible handling of information about our customers and visitors to our websites across the globe.

**Contact Us**

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, any concerns or a complaint regarding our collection and use of your data or a possible breach of your privacy, please write to us at “Contact Us”. We will treat your requests or complaints confidentially. Our representative will contact you within a reasonable time after receipt of your complaint / concern / query to address your same and outline options regarding how they may be resolved or addressed. We will aim to ensure that your complaint / concern / query is resolved in timely and appropriate manner.
